<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cybersec on Salvatore Abello&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://salvatore-abello.github.io/tags/cybersec/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cybersec on Salvatore Abello&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 20:38:20 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://salvatore-abello.github.io/tags/cybersec/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Yet Another PyJail - PySysMagic - L3ak CTF 2024</title>
      <link>https://salvatore-abello.github.io/posts/pysysmagic/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 20:38:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://salvatore-abello.github.io/posts/pysysmagic/</guid>
      <description>I partecipated to the first edition of L3ak CTF with FoocHackz. I solved this challenge, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t hard but writing a working exploit took me at least one/two hours.&#xA;Index Index Overview Source A bit of Py-Magic Obligatory Pyjail Building payloads from docs Solve Flag Considerations Source Overview As the title of the challenge suggests, it&amp;rsquo;s a pyjail. To be more precise, two challenges from two different CTFs were merged together</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-shot CSS Injection - newdiary - 0ctf 2023</title>
      <link>https://salvatore-abello.github.io/posts/newdiary/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://salvatore-abello.github.io/posts/newdiary/</guid>
      <description>This year, for the first time, I partecipated to 0ctf with mhackeroni. Me, @Ricy and @Alemmi solved this challenge, we spent many hours in order to find a working exploit, but it was worth it.&#xA;Index New Diary (14 solves) Index Overview Exploit idea Leaking the nonce Sources CSS exploit First note (ID 0) Second Note (ID 1) Third Note (ID 2) Final exploit Overview This is a whitebox web challenge and it&amp;rsquo;s client-side, we need to steal the admin cookie with the flag inside, so we have to do XSS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My First Writeup - ez-class - B01lers CTF 2023</title>
      <link>https://salvatore-abello.github.io/posts/ezclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://salvatore-abello.github.io/posts/ezclass/</guid>
      <description>I liked this challenge a lot so I decided to create a writeup (my first, actually) about it. Thanks to the organizers for this wonderful CTF!&#xA;Overview This challenge is about a service that gives us the possibility to create and run classes. We can specify:&#xA;The class name The parent class The mumber of methods The method names The method params The method bodies There is no blacklist except for this little one here: ().</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
